This is Qun Qun Rinapon, a.k.a. Inoue Rina!
Today, I’m visiting Bayside Place in Hakata.
Actually, I haven’t had many chances to come to Bayside Place before.
So while I’m really excited, reporting all by myself has me a bit nervous.
[But I’m gonna do my best to stay super positive today!…]
And with that said…
Let’s go!
OK!
We’re here at Wangan Ichiba.
Let’s head on in!
Does Wangan (“coast”) mean Japan?
This market is quintessential Japan.
Much of the fish sold here was caught here in the Hakata area.
Which is your store’s most popular item?
That would be our mackerel fillet.
Wow! It’s so shiny...
...it’s hard to believe it’s a dead fish.
Yes, well we take very fresh fish and dry it immediately,
so it looks much different than your average mackerel.
This way you really get the aji (taste) of the aji (mackerel).
The aji has a lot of aji.
Nice one lady!
“Tempura at the market.”
“We’re open for…” ? (akinai= business)
Let’s go…
Chirin, chirin (ring ring)
Excuse me!
Hello.
Um, it’s a big request, but…
I’ll fry something up for you now.
Really, is that okay?
I didn’t even say anything and he know what I wanted.
Let’s dig in!
These are like “wait carrots can taste this good?” level carrots.
This is their popular menu item, the “Wangan set.”
Shrimp, squid, eel, and lots of veggies.
Thanks for the meal!
Ah, hello.
Hello.
You seem young.
I’m 20.
Wow that’s pretty young to have a fish shop.
…
Do you have any recommendations for fish today?
Actually, we’re kind of low on stock today.
Oh really.
Are these fish originally so shiny?
Are they dipped in something?
Oh no they’re not dipped in anything.
But to keep them from drying out we have them in plastic wrap.
Also I was wondering, was this squid always this color?
That’s octopus.
Hmm. Ok well sorry for taking so much of your time.
You can get back to work.
Thank you very much!
I kept him all to myself.
Next time, Rinapon’s going to the aquarium!
Stay tuned!